Abdush Shomad Bukhori

East Java. Indonesia



XOM.ALBUKHORI@GMAIL.COM



linkedin.com/in/asbukhori

Summary

I am an IT professional with 4+ years of experience in developing web or mobile based applications. Think critically in solving problems effectively and efficiently. Have good communication skills and love to discuss about the issues in application development.

The scope of applications that I have developed include Hospitality, Healthcare, E-Commerce, Onlineshop, Company Profile, Games, E-Vote, Personal Blog and Fintech.

The Featured Technology Stack that I use include Codeigniter Framework, Golang, ReactJS, Flutter, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase.

Experience



Acting Head of IT Department

PT Mamalyfe Selalu Diberkati

Jun 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve business objectives
- Collaborate with the Sales Marketing team to help with the sales process
- Communicate professionally with vendors, IT team, Customer Service team, designer team, content creator team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in applications both backend, frontend, database and server
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Database & Workflow related to developed features
- Guiding the team in developing features according to the design that has been made
- Coding and Testing both Backend (API, Third party Integration) and Frontend (Assist Team when needed)



🙏 IT Project Manager

PT Alfath Technologi Kreatif

Mar 2019 - Apr 2021 (2 years 2 months)

- Create Application required by company and client
- Maintaining the Application that has been created in accordance with the cooperation agreement with the client
- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve application development goals by company and client
- Communicate professionally with IT team, Customer Service team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in the company's own app
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications

- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Workflow related to developed features
- Guiding the team in developing features according to the design that has been made
- Coding and Testing both Backend and Frontend

IT Manager

Kelola.net

Aug 2018 - Apr 2021 (2 years 9 months)

- Create Web Application required by the company
- Maintaining the Web Application that has been created
- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve business objectives
- Collaborate with the Sales Marketing team to help with the sales process
- Communicate professionally with IT team, Customer Service team, designer team, content creator team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in applications both backend, frontend, database and server
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Database & Workflow related to developed features
- Coding and Testing both Backend and Frontend
- Do Online and Offline Training Sessions regarding the Use of Applications for users

Software Developer

Syariahrooms Hospitality

Oct 2017 - Jul 2018 (10 months)

- Create information systems required by the company
- Maintaining the Information System that has been created
- Create features required by the company

Education



Universitas Islam Negeri Maulana Malik Ibrahim

Bachelor's degree, Informatics Engineering Jul 2015 - Nov 2021



Madrasah Aliyah Negeri 2 Gresik

Student, Science 2012 - 2015

Skills

Kotlin • Laravel • Project Estimation • Project Coordination • Firebase • Team Leadership • Project Management • Project Planning • Cross-functional Team Leadership • Codelgniter